http://www.smokehousebbq.com/terms

skip to main content
skip to footer
MenuDinnerLunchCarryoutShippingCatering & DeliveryBanquetKidsOrder OnlineCarryoutDeliveryLocationsKansas CityIndependenceGladstoneAbout UsShippingCatering
My Account
Login
Create an Account
Privacy Policy & TermsPRIVACY POLICY:“We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you visited on the website. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.”SECURITY POLICY:“Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.”REFUND POLICY:“If there is a problem with your transaction please call us at 816-420-9451. Credit will be given in the following way: Store Credit may be issued as a credit in our POS system or as a gift card towards future purchases. In some instances credit will be applied back to your credit card. Please keep all receipts and email to confirm your purchase. Thank you!”Terms Of Service:MODIFICATION OF THESE TERMS OF USE Smokehouse Barbecue reserves the right to change the terms, conditions, and notices under which this website is offered, including but not limited to the charges associated with the use of this website.LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITESThis website may contain links to other websites. The Linked Sites are not under the control of “Smokehouse Barbecue”.“Smokehouse Barbecue” is not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. “Smokehouse Barbecue” is not responsible for webcasting or any other form of transmission received from any Linked Site. “Smokehouse Barbecue” is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by “Smokehouse Barbecue” of the site or any association with its operators.NO UNLAWFUL OR PROHIBITED USEAs a condition of your use of this website, you warrant to “Smokehouse Barbecue” that you will not use the “Smokehouse Barbecue” website for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices. You may not use this Web Site in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair this website or interfere with any other party's use and enjoyment of this website. You may not obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not intentionally made available or provided for through the “Smokehouse Barbecue” websites.USE OF COMMUNICATION SERVICESThis website may contain bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums, communities, personal web pages, calendars, and/or other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with the public at large or with a group (collectively, "Communication Services"), you agree to use the Communication Services only to post, send and receive messages and material that are proper and related to the particular Communication Service. By way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a Communication Service, you will not:Defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others.Publish, post, upload, distribute or disseminate any inappropriate, profane, defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent or unlawful topic, name, material or information.Upload files that contain software or other material protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy of publicity) unless you own or control the rights thereto or have received all necessary consents.Upload files that contain viruses, corrupted files, or any other similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another's computer.Advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any business purpose, unless such Communication Service specifically allows such messages.Conduct or forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes or chain letters.Download any file posted by another user of a Communication Service that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such manner.Falsify or delete any author attributions, legal or other proper notices or proprietary designations or labels of the origin or source of software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded.Restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Communication Services.Violate any code of conduct or other guidelines which may be applicable for any particular Communication Service.Harvest or otherwise collect information about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent.Violate any applicable laws or regulations.“Smokehouse Barbecue” has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However, “Smokehouse Barbecue” reserves the right to review materials posted to a Communication Service and to remove any materials in its sole discretion. “Smokehouse Barbecue” reserves the right to terminate your access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time without notice for any reason whatsoever.“Smokehouse Barbecue” reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, in “Smokehouse Barbecue” sole discretion.Always use caution when giving out any personally identifying information about yourself or your children in any Communication Service. “Smokehouse Barbecue” does not control or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Communication Service and, therefore, “Smokehouse Barbecue” specifically disclaims any liability with regard to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation in any Communication Service. Managers and hosts are not authorized “Smokehouse Barbecue” spokespersons, and their views do not necessarily reflect those of “Smokehouse Barbecue”.Materials uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination. You are responsible for adhering to such limitations if you download the materials.MATERIALS PROVIDED TO “Smokehouse Barbecue” OR POSTED AT ANY of “Smokehouse Barbecue” WEB SITE“Smokehouse Barbecue” does not claim ownership of the materials you provide to “Customer Name” (including feedback and suggestions) or post, upload, input or submit to any “Smokehouse Barbecue” Web Site or its associated services (collectively "Submissions"). However, by posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your Submission you are granting “Smokehouse Barbecue”, its affiliated companies and necessary sublicensees permission to use your Submission in connection with the operation of their Internet businesses including, without limitation, the rights to: copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and reformat your Submission; and to publish your name in connection with your Submission.No compensation will be paid with respect to the use of your Submission, as provided herein. “Smokehouse Barbecue” is under no obligation to post or use any Submission you may provide and may remove any Submission at any time in “Smokehouse Barbecue” sole discretion.By posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your Submission you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your Submission as described in this section including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the Submissions.LIABILITY DISCLAIMERTHE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. “Smokehouse Barbecue” AND /OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE “Smokehouse Barbecue” WEBSITE AT ANY TIME. ADVICE RECEIVED VIA “Smokehouse Barbecue” WEBSITE SHOULD NOT BE RELIED UPON FOR PERSONAL, MEDICAL, LEGAL OR FINANCIAL DECISIONS AND YOU SHOULD CONSULT AN APPROPRIATE PROFESSIONAL FOR SPECIFIC ADVICE TAILORED TO YOUR SITUATION.“Smokehouse Barbecue” AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY, RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED ON THIS WEBSITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ALL SUCH INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. “Smokehouse Barbecue” AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THIS INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS, INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL “Smokehouse Barbecue” AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE “Smokehouse Barbecue” WEB SITE, WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEB SITE OR RELATED SERVICES, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE h4th.org WEB SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THIS WEB SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF “Smokehouse Barbecue” OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY PORTION OF THIS WEB SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THIS WEB SITE.TERMINATION/ACCESS RESTRICTION“Smokehouse Barbecue” reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to this website and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without notice. GENERAL To the maximum extent permitted by law, this agreement is governed by the laws of Missouri, U.S.A. and you hereby consent to the exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in Kansas City, Missouri, U.S.A. in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of this website. Use of this website is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these terms and conditions, including without limitation this paragraph. You agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship exists between you and “Smokehouse Barbecue” as a result of this agreement or use of this website. “Smokehouse Barbecue” performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal process, and nothing contained in this agreement is in derogation of “Smokehouse Barbecue” right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or requirements relating to your use of this website or information provided to or gathered by “Smokehouse Barbecue” with respect to such use. If any part of this agreement is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of the agreement shall continue in effect. Unless otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement between the user and “Smokehouse Barbecue” with respect to this website and it supersedes all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or written, between the user and “Smokehouse Barbecue” with respect to this website. A printed version of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related documents be drawn up in English.COPYRIGHT AND TRADEMARK NOTICES:All contents of the website are: Copyright “Smokehouse Barbecue” and/or its suppliers. All rights reserved.
Home|About Us|Carryout|Delivery|Shipping|Catering|Terms & Conditions|LoginFollow UsMenusDinnerLunchCarryoutShippingCatering & DeliveryBanquetKidsLocationsKansas CityIndependenceGladstoneMailing ListemailJoin NowJoin Our TeamApply HereCopyright © 2020 All Rights Reserved.OrderezeLogin
